In this video, I'm going to show you how to find out what you've made.com.
So log into your profile on the AdultWork.com website, go to my details,
credits, and go
along to credit statement, click.
And to find out what you've made each day, I'm going to show you what to do.
So you always start off with what you've made at the end of the day.
So at the end of the day here, you are on 381 credits, 0.90.
So you're going to type that into your calculator, 381.90, and that's the end
of the day as you
can see.
That's where you start.
Then we're going to go back up to the start of the day.
So let's see, okay, so you started here, so we're going to go across, and here
you can
see it's 323.61, so we're going to minus that from the bottom figure, from this
figure
here.
So as you've already typed this into your calculator, you just want to minus
this.
So I have my calculator 381.90, and then we're going to minus 323.61, and then
hit equals.
So that's 58.29 credits, so that's what you've made in this day on the 24th.
Obviously, this isn't your profile, this is just a demo just to show you.
And then to find out how much you've earned in pounds, I'll show you how to do
that now.
So it's a little credit or a little bit different to pounds.
You get a certain amount of each of your credits, so all you have to do is
whatever your final
figure is in the calculator, so obviously today ours is 58.29.
You just subtract a certain percentage from that.
So if you just do minus 43.5% and press equals, it'll tell you what you've made
that day.
The reason why we minus 43.5% is because that's how much less taken from you.
AdultWork, take 30%.
We take 10%, and the payroll company take 3.5%, which makes 43.5%, so we take
that away from
the total.
And I've just done that in the calculator, and that comes to 32.9 pounds.
So that's how much you've made in that day.
We pay every single day, but you have to hit a 35 pound payout target.
If you don't hit this, then it'll just sit in your balance until the next time
you work.
So obviously this profile is on 32.9, so she won't be paid tomorrow, she'll be
paid when
she pushes that over 35.
So the next time she goes online, obviously she's likely to hit in at least a
couple of
pounds, and the next day it'll go into her account.
I hope all that makes sense.
If you have any issues with any phone, please just contact your mentor and she
will help
you through all of this.